

Location

Pekalongan, Indonesia

Phone

(+62) 878 9471 0683

Email

choirulchuluq10@gmail.com

Github ID

@chuluq

Languages

Indonesia

English

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

ReactJS

NextJS

React Native

Redux

Moch Chaerul Chuluq

Front End

Web Responsive - Mobile

JavaScript is my "native" programming language, I have worked with it for 1 year. I am familiar with React, NextJS, or React Native. Redux is my option of state management when I need global state a lot. I can use either Redux Toolkit or Redux Saga.

Experience

Jul 2021 — Present

Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Teravin Technovation

Feb 2021 — Jun 2021 Yogyakarta, Indonesia Front End Carakan

Front End

Jun 2019 — Jul 2019

Full Stack Internship

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Solusi 247

Education

2020 BSc, Information and Communication Technology
Prince of Songkla University, Thailand

2016 High School Diploma
SMA Negeri 3, Pekalongan

2013 Middle School Diploma
SMP Salafiyah, Pekalongan

2010 Primary School Diploma
MSI 01, Pekalongan